[
  {
    "SerialNo": 1,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 2,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a popular general-purpose programming language and computing platform. It is fast, reliable, and secure. According to Oracle, the company that owns Java, Java runs on 3 billion devices worldwide."
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 3,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 4,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a popular general-purpose programming language and computing platform. It is fast, reliable, and secure. According to Oracle, the company that owns Java, Java runs on 3 billion devices worldwide."
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 5,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 6,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 7,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a popular general-purpose programming language and computing platform. It is fast, reliable, and secure. According to Oracle, the company that owns Java, Java runs on 3 billion devices worldwide."
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 8,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 9,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 10,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "Java is a high level programming language"
  },
  {
    "SerialNo": 10,
    "Question": "What is Java?",
    "Answer": "package google;\n\npublic class Model {\n\t\n\tString name;\n\tpublic String getName() {\n\t\treturn name;\n\t}\n\tpublic void setName(String name) {\n\t\tthis.name = name;\n\t}\n\tpublic int getRollNo() {\n\t\treturn rollNo;\n\t}\n\tpublic void setRollNo(int rollNo) {\n\t\tthis.rollNo = rollNo;\n\t}\n\tint rollNo;\n\t\n}\n"
  }
]